I am Rajeev Kumar Chief Investment
Officer at Big Profit Securities I have
given investors 120% returns in
just 10 months Do you also want guaranteed returns
Join my chat group Hey
[music]
Wow this is all set Assured IPO allocations
10% guaranteed returns Download the pop
now Total payment towards IPO instant
4tune limited only 50 lakhs now This is
all set
not set it is setup Check to whom you are making the payment
and block them Don't
fall for these sets Block the
fraudsters Financial institutions
never promise any short returns in equity
Verify before joining investment related chat groups To
report investment fraud
call 1930 or
visit www.cybercrime.gov.in
Issued in public interest by AAA
Foundation